[
    {
        "question": "How many unique values are possible using a single binary digit?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "4",
            "8",
            "9",
            "16" 
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What terms represent the maximum and actual speed that can be utilized by a device to transfer data?",
        "options": [
            "bandwidth; throughput",
            "throughput; bandwidth",
            "bandwidth; goodput",
            "throughput; goodput"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "bandwidth; throughput"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which factor classifies a host as a server?",
        "options": [
            "the CPU speed",
            "the software installed",
            "the amount of memory",
            "the network connection"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the software installed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which term is used to describe a network device that relies on another device to obtain information?",
        "options": [
            "web server",
            "console",
            "server",
            "client"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "client"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a disadvantage of deploying a peer-to-peer network model?",
        "options": [
            "difficulty of setup",
            "lack of centralized administration",
            "high degree of complexity",
            "high cost"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "lack of centralized administration"
    },
    {
        "question": "A user is looking for a wireless headphone for listening to songs stored on a smartphone. What wireless technology would the headphone use?",
        "options": [
            "3G/4G",
            "Wi-Fi",
            "infrared",
            "Bluetooth"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bluetooth"
    },
    {
        "question": "A consumer places a smartphone close to a pay terminal at a store and the shopping charge is successfully paid. Which type of wireless technology was used?",
        "options": [
            "Bluetooth",
            "NFC",
            "Wi-Fi",
            "3G"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "NFC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network component can be used to share an attached printer to the network?",
        "options": [
            "personal computer",
            "peripheral",
            "access point",
            "network media"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "personal computer"
    },
    {
        "question": "A wireless network was recently installed in a coffee shop and customer mobile devices are not receiving network configuration information. What should be done to correct the problem?",
        "options": [
            "Check the connection of the DNS server to the Internet.",
            "Provide peripheral devices to customers.",
            "Make sure the DHCP server is functional.",
            "Ensure that the default gateway device is working properly."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Make sure the DHCP server is functional."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which network device is used to translate a domain name to the associated IP address?",
        "options": [
            "router",
            "DNS server",
            "DHCP server",
            "default gateway"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DNS server"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you were drawing a physical topology of your school network, what type of information would you include?",
        "options": [
            "how devices are connected",
            "the location of devices in the building",
            "the path that data takes to reach destinations",
            "the IP addresses of all devices on the network"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the location of devices in the building"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. An instructor wants to show a few prebuilt Packet Tracer sample labs in class. Which menu option would the instructor use to access a sample lab?",
        "options": [
            "File",
            "Edit",
            "Options",
            "View",
            "Tools",
            "Extensions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "File"
    },
    {
        "question": "When authenticating within Packet Tracer, which two items could you use? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "a previously configured PIN",
            "a previously configured pattern",
            "a username associated with NetAcad",
            "a username associated with a specific school",
            "an email address found in the NetAcad profile"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a username associated with NetAcad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A student has started a Packet Tracer network that includes a home wireless router to be used for both wired and wireless devices. The router and laptop have been placed within the logical workspace. The student clicks on the laptop and the window that opens is shown in the exhibit. What is the purpose of the modules on the left?",
        "options": [
            "This is the list of modules currently installed in the laptop.",
            "These are optional modules that can be installed into the module slot if it is currently empty.",
            "These are modules that can be used by double-clicking on one module so that it automatically installs into the laptop.",
            "This is a list of modules available from the manufacturer that can be clicked on and \u201cpurchased.\u201d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "These are optional modules that can be installed into the module slot if it is currently empty."
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A student is creating a wired and wireless network in Packet Tracer. After inserting a router, switch, and PC, the student chooses a straight-through cable to connect the PC to the switch. Which connection would be the best port for the student to choose on the PC?",
        "options": [
            "RS 232",
            "USB0",
            "USB1",
            "FastEthernet0"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "FastEthernet0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Which menu item would be used to bring up a command prompt environment to be able to ping another network device?",
        "options": [
            "Physical",
            "Config",
            "Desktop",
            "Programming",
            "Attributes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Desktop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A home wireless network is being configured within Packet Tracer. The user adds a wireless router, a PC, and three laptops. The user is reviewing the wireless connection on one of the laptops. What can be determined?",
        "options": [
            "Because the password is not enabled, the laptop cannot connect to the wireless router.",
            "All three laptops are connected to the wireless network successfully.",
            "The laptop is connected to a wireless network.",
            "The laptop must have a different wireless NIC installed before being able to connect to the wireless router."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The laptop is connected to a wireless network."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network cable is commonly used to connect office computers to the local network?",
        "options": [
            "coaxial cable",
            "twisted-pair cable",
            "glass fiber-optic cable",
            "plastic fiber-optic cable"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "twisted-pair cable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which criterion can be used to select the appropriate type of network media for a network?",
        "options": [
            "the types of data that need to be prioritized",
            "the cost of the end devices that are used in the network",
            "the number of intermediary devices that are installed in the network",
            "the environment where the selected medium is to be installed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the environment where the selected medium is to be installed"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are two sources of electromagnetic interference that can affect data transmissions? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "LED monitor",
            "microwave oven",
            "infrared remote control",
            "cordless phone",
            "florescent light fixture"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "microwave oven"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are two advantages of using fiber-optic cabling to interconnect devices? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "Fiber-optic cable is immune from EMI and RFI.",
            "Fiber-optic cables can extend several miles.",
            "Fiber-optic cables use extra shielding to protect copper wires.",
            "Fiber-optic cables are easy to install..",
            "Fiber-optic cables are commonly found in both homes and small businesses."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fiber-optic cable is immune from EMI and RFI."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network cable is used to connect the components that make up satellite communication systems?",
        "options": [
            "coaxial",
            "fiber-optic",
            "shielded twisted-pair",
            "unshielded twisted-pair"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "coaxial"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement describes the use of the ping command?",
        "options": [
            "The ping command tests end-to-end connectivity between two devices.",
            "The ping command can be used to determine the exact location of the problem when troubleshooting reachability issues.",
            "The ping command can be used to test reachability using the physical address of the device.",
            "The ping command shows current Layer 4 sessions."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The ping command tests end-to-end connectivity between two devices."
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of protocols in data communications?",
        "options": [
            "specifying the bandwidth of the channel or medium for each type of communication",
            "specifying the device operating systems that will support the communication",
            "providing the rules required for a specific type of communication to occur",
            "dictating the content of the message sent during communication"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "providing the rules required for a specific type of communication to occur"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two OSI model layers have the same functionality as two layers of the TCP/IP model? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "data link",
            "network",
            "physical",
            "session",
            "transport"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "network"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three layers of the OSI model map to the application layer of the TCP/IP model? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "application",
            "presentation",
            "session",
            "data link",
            "transport",
            "network"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "application"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network model describes the functions that must be completed at a particular layer, but does not specify exactly how each protocol should work?",
        "options": [
            "TCP/IP model",
            "protocol model",
            "reference model",
            "hierarchical design model"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "reference model"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers is responsible for standards in which two areas? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "TCP/IP technologies",
            "the OSI reference model",
            "wireless LANs",
            "peer-to-peer application compliance",
            "Ethernet media access control",
            "IP address allocation and management"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "wireless LANs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement is true about MAC addresses?",
        "options": [
            "MAC addresses are implemented by software.",
            "A NIC only needs a MAC address if connected to a WAN.",
            "The first three bytes are used by the vendor assigned OUI.",
            "The ISO is responsible for MAC addresses regulations."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The first three bytes are used by the vendor assigned OUI."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is indicated by the 100 in the 100BASE-T standard?\u200b",
        "options": [
            "meters",
            "feet",
            "megabits per second",
            "twists per meter"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "megabits per second"
    },
    {
        "question": "What process is used to place one message inside another message for transfer from the source to the destination?",
        "options": [
            "access control",
            "decoding",
            "encapsulation",
            "flow control"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "encapsulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which logical address is used for delivery of data to a remote network?",
        "options": [
            "destination MAC address",
            "destination IP address",
            "destination port number",
            "source MAC address",
            "source IP address"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "destination IP address"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three layers of a hierarchical network design model? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "network",
            "Internet",
            "access",
            "core",
            "application",
            "distribution"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "access"
    },
    {
        "question": "What addressing information is recorded by a switch to build its MAC address table?",
        "options": [
            "the destination Layer 3 address of incoming packets",
            "the destination Layer 2 address of outgoing frames",
            "the source Layer 3 address of outgoing packets",
            "the source Layer 2 address of incoming frames"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the source Layer 2 address of incoming frames"
    },
    {
        "question": "A small publishing company has a network design such that when a broadcast is sent on the LAN, 200 devices receive the transmitted broadcast. How can the network administrator reduce the number of devices that receive broadcast traffic?",
        "options": [
            "Add more switches so that fewer devices are on a particular switch.",
            "Replace the switches with switches that have more ports per switch. This will allow more devices on a particular switch.",
            "Segment the LAN into smaller LANs and route between them.",
            "Replace at least half of the switches with hubs to reduce the size of the broadcast domain."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Segment the LAN into smaller LANs and route between them."
    },
    {
        "question": "What action does the ARP process take when a host needs to build a frame, but the ARP cache does not contain an address mapping?",
        "options": [
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the IPv4 address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the IPv4 broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the IPv4 broadcast address to discover the IPv4 address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device."
    },
    {
        "question": "What will a Cisco LAN switch do if it receives an incoming frame and the destination MAC address is not listed in the MAC address table?",
        "options": [
            "Drop the frame.",
            "Send the frame to the default gateway address.",
            "Use ARP to resolve the port that is related to the frame.",
            "Forward the frame out all ports except the port where the frame is received."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Forward the frame out all ports except the port where the frame is received."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two functions are primary functions of a router? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "packet forwarding",
            "microsegmentation",
            "domain name resolution",
            "path selection",
            "flow control"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "packet forwarding"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Consider the IP address configuration shown from PC1. What is a description of the default gateway address?",
        "options": [
            "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the company to the Internet.",
            "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the PC1 LAN to Router1.",
            "It is the IP address of Switch1 that connects PC1 to other devices on the same LAN.",
            "It is the IP address of the ISP network device located in the cloud."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the PC1 LAN to Router1."
    },
    {
        "question": "A computer can access devices on the same network but cannot access devices on other networks. What is the probable cause of this problem?",
        "options": [
            "The cable is not connected properly to the NIC.",
            "The computer has an invalid IP address.",
            "The computer has an incorrect subnet mask.",
            "The computer has an invalid default gateway address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The computer has an invalid default gateway address."
    },
    {
        "question": "A router receives an incoming packet and determines that the packet should be forwarded to a remote destination host. What will the router do to forward the packet?",
        "options": [
            "It encapsulates the frame with a source IP address by using the specific IP address of the destination host.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with a destination MAC address by using the specific MAC address of the destination host device.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with the destination IP address by using the specific IP address configured on the interface of the next hop router.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with the destination MAC address by using the MAC address of the interface of the next-hop router."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It encapsulates the frame with the destination MAC address by using the MAC address of the interface of the next-hop router."
    },
    {
        "question": "A router is receiving a stream of incoming packets and does not contain a route to the remote destination network. What configuration can a network administrator issue in order to successfully forward the incoming packets?",
        "options": [
            "Add a default route.",
            "Enable a dynamic routing protocol.",
            "Share the routing table with the hosts on the local network.",
            "Change the IP address of the ingress interface to match the targeted destination network."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Add a default route."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two parts are components of an IPv4 address? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "subnet portion",
            "network portion",
            "logical portion",
            "host portion",
            "physical portion",
            "broadcast portion"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "network portion"
    },
    {
        "question": "When a host sends a packet, how does it determine if the destination of the packet is on the same local network or on a remote network?",
        "options": [
            "It checks to see if the default gateway is configured.",
            "It compares the source and destination MAC addresses.",
            "It queries the DNS server with the destination IP address.",
            "It uses the subnet mask to compare the source and destination IP address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It uses the subnet mask to compare the source and destination IP address."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default subnet mask for an IP address of 198.133.219.4?",
        "options": [
            "255.0.0.0",
            "255.255.0.0",
            "255.255.255.0",
            "255.255.255.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "255.255.255.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three IP addresses are private ? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "10.1.1.1",
            "172.32.5.2",
            "192.167.10.10",
            "172.16.4.4",
            "192.168.5.5",
            "224.6.6.6"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10.1.1.1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of message is sent to a specific group of hosts?",
        "options": [
            "unicast",
            "dynamic",
            "multicast",
            "broadcast"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "multicast"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which IP address is a unicast address if a default subnet mask is used?",
        "options": [
            "201.34.45.0",
            "192.16.43.67",
            "226.34.15.78",
            "195.124.45.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "192.16.43.67"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three types of nodes should be assigned static IP addresses on a network? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "servers",
            "desktop PCs",
            "mobile laptops",
            "printers",
            "gateways",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "servers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is DHCP for IPv4 preferred for use on large networks?",
        "options": [
            "Large networks send more requests for domain to IP address resolution than do smaller networks.",
            "DHCP uses a reliable transport layer protocol.",
            "It prevents sharing of files that are copyrighted.",
            "It is a more efficient way to manage IPv4 addresses than static address assignment is.",
            "Hosts on large networks require more IPv4 addressing configuration settings than do hosts on small networks."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It is a more efficient way to manage IPv4 addresses than static address assignment is."
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. PC1 is configured to obtain a dynamic IP address from the DHCP server. PC1 has been shut down for two weeks. When PC1 boots and tries to request an available IP address, which destination IP address will PC1 place in the IP header?",
        "options": [
            "192.168.1.1",
            "192.168.1.8",
            "192.168.1.255",
            "255.255.255.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "255.255.255.255"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which message does an IPv4 host use to reply when it receives a DHCPOFFER message from a DHCP server?",
        "options": [
            "DHCPACK",
            "DHCPDISCOVER",
            "DHCPOFFER",
            "DHCPREQUEST"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DHCPREQUEST"
    },
    {
        "question": "A host PC is attempting to lease an address through DHCP. What message is sent by the server to let the client know it is able to use the provided IP information?",
        "options": [
            "DHCPDISCOVER",
            "DHCPOFFER",
            "DHCPREQUEST",
            "DHCPACK",
            "DHCPNACK"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DHCPACK"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is a DHCPDISCOVER transmitted on a network to reach a DHCP server?",
        "options": [
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the IP address of the DHCP server as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with a multicast IP address that all DHCP servers listen to as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the broadcast IP address as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the IP address of the default gateway as the destination address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the broadcast IP address as the destination address."
    },
    {
        "question": "A DHCP server is used to assign IP addresses dynamically to the hosts on a network. The address pool is configured with 172.30.8.0/24. There are 7 printers on this network that need to use reserved static IP addresses from the pool. How many IP addresses in the pool are left to be assigned to other hosts?",
        "options": [
            "254",
            "247",
            "251",
            "249"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "An employee is having connectivity issues. Why might a network technician try to ping the default gateway from the employee laptop?",
        "options": [
            "to verify that an IP address was provided by the DHCP server",
            "to determine if the laptop address is included in the DNS server",
            "to verify that the SVI interface on the switch is configured correctly",
            "to verify connectivity with the device that provides access to remote networks"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to verify connectivity with the device that provides access to remote networks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result if the default gateway address is misconfigured on a PC?",
        "options": [
            "The PC cannot communicate with any devices.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices both in remote networks and in the same network.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices in the same network but not with those in remote networks.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices in remote networks but not with those in the same network."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The PC can communicate with devices in the same network but not with those in remote networks."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement accurately describes dynamic NAT?",
        "options": [
            "It always maps a private IP address to a public IP address.",
            "It provides an automated mapping of inside local to inside global IP addresses.",
            "It provides a mapping of internal host names to IP addresses.",
            "It dynamically provides IP addressing to internal hosts."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It provides an automated mapping of inside local to inside global IP addresses."
    },
    {
        "question": "What purpose does NAT64 serve in IPv6?",
        "options": [
            "It converts IPv6 packets into IPv4 packets.",
            "It translates private IPv6 addresses into public IPv6 addresses.",
            "It enables companies to use IPv6 unique local addresses in the network.",
            "It converts regular IPv6 addresses into 64-bit addresses that can be used on the Internet.",
            "It converts the 48-bit MAC address into a 64-bit host address that can be used for automatic host addressing."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It converts IPv6 packets into IPv4 packets."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of IPv6 address is not routable and used only for communication on a single subnet?",
        "options": [
            "global unicast address",
            "link-local address",
            "loopback address",
            "unique local address",
            "unspecified address"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "link-local address"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bits make up the single IPv6 hextet :10CD:?",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "8",
            "16",
            "32"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the valid most compressed format possible of the IPv6 address 2001:0DB8:0000:AB00:0000:0000:0000:1234?",
        "options": [
            "2001:DB8:0:AB00::1234",
            "2001:DB8:0:AB::1234",
            "2001:DB8::AB00::1234",
            "2001:DB8:0:AB:0:1234"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2001:DB8:0:AB00::1234"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three pieces of information are identified by a URL? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "the MAC address of the web server",
            "the protocol that is being used",
            "the domain name that is being accessed",
            "the IP address of the gateway",
            "the version of the browser",
            "the location of the resource"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the protocol that is being used"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an advantage of UDP over TCP?",
        "options": [
            "UDP communication requires less overhead.",
            "UDP communication is more reliable.",
            "UDP reorders segments that are received out of order.",
            "UDP acknowledges received data."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "UDP communication requires less overhead."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of applications are best suited to use UDP as the transport layer protocol?",
        "options": [
            "applications that require flow control",
            "applications that require data to be reassembled in a specific order",
            "applications that require minimal transmission delay",
            "applications that require stateful sessions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "applications that require minimal transmission delay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What layer of the TCP/IP suite makes sure that all the data packets of a message arrive safely at the destination?",
        "options": [
            "internet",
            "transport",
            "application",
            "network access"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "transport"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does a client computer determine what source port number to assign to a UDP header?",
        "options": [
            "The port number is random within the range of dynamic port numbers.",
            "The port number is based on the application that created the data.",
            "The port number is based on a well-known port number that is open on the destination device.",
            "The port number is based on a well-known port number that is assigned to the application on the sending device."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The port number is random within the range of dynamic port numbers."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a socket?",
        "options": [
            "the combination of the source and destination IP address and source and destination Ethernet address",
            "the combination of a source IP address and port number or a destination IP address and port number",
            "the combination of the source and destination sequence and acknowledgment numbers",
            "the combination of the source and destination sequence numbers and port numbers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the combination of a source IP address and port number or a destination IP address and port number"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using a source port number in a TCP communication?",
        "options": [
            "to notify the remote device that the conversation is over",
            "to assemble the segments that arrived out of order",
            "to keep track of multiple conversations between devices",
            "to inquire for a nonreceived segment"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to keep track of multiple conversations between devices"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two protocols are used in the process of sending and receiving emails? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "HTTP",
            "POP",
            "SSH",
            "SMTP",
            "FTP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "POP"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a function of a DNS server?",
        "options": [
            "It determines the IP address that is associated with a specific host domain name.",
            "It maps IP addresses to physical addresses.",
            "It translates private IP addresses to public IP addresses.",
            "It assigns logical address information to host computers."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It determines the IP address that is associated with a specific host domain name."
    },
    {
        "question": "Open the PT Activity. Perform the tasks in the activity instructions and then answer the question.",
        "options": [
            "192.168.10.1",
            "192.168.10.100",
            "209.165.201.3",
            "209.165.201.4"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "209.165.201.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Open the PT Activity. Perform the tasks in the activity instructions and then answer the question.",
        "options": [
            "A secure web server is the way to go!",
            "A web server should run secure services!",
            "A web server provides secure communication!",
            "A secure web server is running!"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A secure web server is the way to go!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two applications provide virtual terminal access to remote servers? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "SSH",
            "DNS",
            "DHCP",
            "SMTP",
            "Telnet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "SSH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of server would use IMAP?",
        "options": [
            "DNS",
            "DHCP",
            "email",
            "FTP",
            "Telnet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "email"
    },
    {
        "title":"When did the programming language C++ came out?",
        "choices":[
            1997,
            1995,
            2000,
            1998
        ],
        "correctAnswer":3
    },
    {
        "title":"When Node.js came out?",
        "choices":[
            2010,
            2011,
            2009,
            2006
        ],
        "correctAnswer":2
    },
    {
        "title":"What brand of laptop do I have?",
        "choices":[
            "HP",
            "Acer",
            "Dell",
            "Lenovo"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":0
    },
    {
        "title":"How old am I?",
        "choices":[
            12,
            20,
            9,
            16
        ],
        "correctAnswer":3
    },
    {
        "title":"How old is Google?",
        "choices":[
            12,
            20,
            18,
            16
        ],
        "correctAnswer":2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many unique values are possible using a single binary digit?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "4",
            "8",
            "9",
            "16" 
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What terms represent the maximum and actual speed that can be utilized by a device to transfer data?",
        "options": [
            "bandwidth; throughput",
            "throughput; bandwidth",
            "bandwidth; goodput",
            "throughput; goodput"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "bandwidth; throughput"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which factor classifies a host as a server?",
        "options": [
            "the CPU speed",
            "the software installed",
            "the amount of memory",
            "the network connection"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the software installed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which term is used to describe a network device that relies on another device to obtain information?",
        "options": [
            "web server",
            "console",
            "server",
            "client"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "client"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a disadvantage of deploying a peer-to-peer network model?",
        "options": [
            "difficulty of setup",
            "lack of centralized administration",
            "high degree of complexity",
            "high cost"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "lack of centralized administration"
    },
    {
        "question": "A user is looking for a wireless headphone for listening to songs stored on a smartphone. What wireless technology would the headphone use?",
        "options": [
            "3G/4G",
            "Wi-Fi",
            "infrared",
            "Bluetooth"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bluetooth"
    },
    {
        "question": "A consumer places a smartphone close to a pay terminal at a store and the shopping charge is successfully paid. Which type of wireless technology was used?",
        "options": [
            "Bluetooth",
            "NFC",
            "Wi-Fi",
            "3G"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "NFC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network component can be used to share an attached printer to the network?",
        "options": [
            "personal computer",
            "peripheral",
            "access point",
            "network media"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "personal computer"
    },
    {
        "question": "A wireless network was recently installed in a coffee shop and customer mobile devices are not receiving network configuration information. What should be done to correct the problem?",
        "options": [
            "Check the connection of the DNS server to the Internet.",
            "Provide peripheral devices to customers.",
            "Make sure the DHCP server is functional.",
            "Ensure that the default gateway device is working properly."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Make sure the DHCP server is functional."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which network device is used to translate a domain name to the associated IP address?",
        "options": [
            "router",
            "DNS server",
            "DHCP server",
            "default gateway"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DNS server"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you were drawing a physical topology of your school network, what type of information would you include?",
        "options": [
            "how devices are connected",
            "the location of devices in the building",
            "the path that data takes to reach destinations",
            "the IP addresses of all devices on the network"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the location of devices in the building"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. An instructor wants to show a few prebuilt Packet Tracer sample labs in class. Which menu option would the instructor use to access a sample lab?",
        "options": [
            "File",
            "Edit",
            "Options",
            "View",
            "Tools",
            "Extensions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "File"
    },
    {
        "question": "When authenticating within Packet Tracer, which two items could you use? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "a previously configured PIN",
            "a previously configured pattern",
            "a username associated with NetAcad",
            "a username associated with a specific school",
            "an email address found in the NetAcad profile"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a username associated with NetAcad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A student has started a Packet Tracer network that includes a home wireless router to be used for both wired and wireless devices. The router and laptop have been placed within the logical workspace. The student clicks on the laptop and the window that opens is shown in the exhibit. What is the purpose of the modules on the left?",
        "options": [
            "This is the list of modules currently installed in the laptop.",
            "These are optional modules that can be installed into the module slot if it is currently empty.",
            "These are modules that can be used by double-clicking on one module so that it automatically installs into the laptop.",
            "This is a list of modules available from the manufacturer that can be clicked on and \u201cpurchased.\u201d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "These are optional modules that can be installed into the module slot if it is currently empty."
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A student is creating a wired and wireless network in Packet Tracer. After inserting a router, switch, and PC, the student chooses a straight-through cable to connect the PC to the switch. Which connection would be the best port for the student to choose on the PC?",
        "options": [
            "RS 232",
            "USB0",
            "USB1",
            "FastEthernet0"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "FastEthernet0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Which menu item would be used to bring up a command prompt environment to be able to ping another network device?",
        "options": [
            "Physical",
            "Config",
            "Desktop",
            "Programming",
            "Attributes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Desktop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A home wireless network is being configured within Packet Tracer. The user adds a wireless router, a PC, and three laptops. The user is reviewing the wireless connection on one of the laptops. What can be determined?",
        "options": [
            "Because the password is not enabled, the laptop cannot connect to the wireless router.",
            "All three laptops are connected to the wireless network successfully.",
            "The laptop is connected to a wireless network.",
            "The laptop must have a different wireless NIC installed before being able to connect to the wireless router."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The laptop is connected to a wireless network."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network cable is commonly used to connect office computers to the local network?",
        "options": [
            "coaxial cable",
            "twisted-pair cable",
            "glass fiber-optic cable",
            "plastic fiber-optic cable"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "twisted-pair cable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which criterion can be used to select the appropriate type of network media for a network?",
        "options": [
            "the types of data that need to be prioritized",
            "the cost of the end devices that are used in the network",
            "the number of intermediary devices that are installed in the network",
            "the environment where the selected medium is to be installed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the environment where the selected medium is to be installed"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are two sources of electromagnetic interference that can affect data transmissions? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "LED monitor",
            "microwave oven",
            "infrared remote control",
            "cordless phone",
            "florescent light fixture"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "microwave oven"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are two advantages of using fiber-optic cabling to interconnect devices? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "Fiber-optic cable is immune from EMI and RFI.",
            "Fiber-optic cables can extend several miles.",
            "Fiber-optic cables use extra shielding to protect copper wires.",
            "Fiber-optic cables are easy to install..",
            "Fiber-optic cables are commonly found in both homes and small businesses."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fiber-optic cable is immune from EMI and RFI."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network cable is used to connect the components that make up satellite communication systems?",
        "options": [
            "coaxial",
            "fiber-optic",
            "shielded twisted-pair",
            "unshielded twisted-pair"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "coaxial"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement describes the use of the ping command?",
        "options": [
            "The ping command tests end-to-end connectivity between two devices.",
            "The ping command can be used to determine the exact location of the problem when troubleshooting reachability issues.",
            "The ping command can be used to test reachability using the physical address of the device.",
            "The ping command shows current Layer 4 sessions."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The ping command tests end-to-end connectivity between two devices."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of protocols in data communications?",
        "options": [
            "specifying the bandwidth of the channel or medium for each type of communication",
            "specifying the device operating systems that will support the communication",
            "providing the rules required for a specific type of communication to occur",
            "dictating the content of the message sent during communication"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "providing the rules required for a specific type of communication to occur"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two OSI model layers have the same functionality as two layers of the TCP/IP model? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "data link",
            "network",
            "physical",
            "session",
            "transport"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "network"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three layers of the OSI model map to the application layer of the TCP/IP model? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "application",
            "presentation",
            "session",
            "data link",
            "transport",
            "network"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "application"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of network model describes the functions that must be completed at a particular layer, but does not specify exactly how each protocol should work?",
        "options": [
            "TCP/IP model",
            "protocol model",
            "reference model",
            "hierarchical design model"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "reference model"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers is responsible for standards in which two areas? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "TCP/IP technologies",
            "the OSI reference model",
            "wireless LANs",
            "peer-to-peer application compliance",
            "Ethernet media access control",
            "IP address allocation and management"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "wireless LANs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement is true about MAC addresses?",
        "options": [
            "MAC addresses are implemented by software.",
            "A NIC only needs a MAC address if connected to a WAN.",
            "The first three bytes are used by the vendor assigned OUI.",
            "The ISO is responsible for MAC addresses regulations."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The first three bytes are used by the vendor assigned OUI."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is indicated by the 100 in the 100BASE-T standard?\u200b",
        "options": [
            "meters",
            "feet",
            "megabits per second",
            "twists per meter"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "megabits per second"
    },
    {
        "question": "What process is used to place one message inside another message for transfer from the source to the destination?",
        "options": [
            "access control",
            "decoding",
            "encapsulation",
            "flow control"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "encapsulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which logical address is used for delivery of data to a remote network?",
        "options": [
            "destination MAC address",
            "destination IP address",
            "destination port number",
            "source MAC address",
            "source IP address"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "destination IP address"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three layers of a hierarchical network design model? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "network",
            "Internet",
            "access",
            "core",
            "application",
            "distribution"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "access"
    },
    {
        "question": "What addressing information is recorded by a switch to build its MAC address table?",
        "options": [
            "the destination Layer 3 address of incoming packets",
            "the destination Layer 2 address of outgoing frames",
            "the source Layer 3 address of outgoing packets",
            "the source Layer 2 address of incoming frames"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the source Layer 2 address of incoming frames"
    },
    {
        "question": "A small publishing company has a network design such that when a broadcast is sent on the LAN, 200 devices receive the transmitted broadcast. How can the network administrator reduce the number of devices that receive broadcast traffic?",
        "options": [
            "Add more switches so that fewer devices are on a particular switch.",
            "Replace the switches with switches that have more ports per switch. This will allow more devices on a particular switch.",
            "Segment the LAN into smaller LANs and route between them.",
            "Replace at least half of the switches with hubs to reduce the size of the broadcast domain."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Segment the LAN into smaller LANs and route between them."
    },
    {
        "question": "What action does the ARP process take when a host needs to build a frame, but the ARP cache does not contain an address mapping?",
        "options": [
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the IPv4 address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the IPv4 broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the IPv4 broadcast address to discover the IPv4 address of the destination device.",
            "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The ARP process sends out an ARP request to the Ethernet broadcast address to discover the MAC address of the destination device."
    },
    {
        "question": "What will a Cisco LAN switch do if it receives an incoming frame and the destination MAC address is not listed in the MAC address table?",
        "options": [
      /      "Drop the frame.",
            "Send the frame to the default gateway address.",
            "Use ARP to resolve the port that is related to the frame.",
            "Forward the frame out all ports except the port where the frame is received."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Forward the frame out all ports except the port where the frame is received."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two functions are primary functions of a router? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "packet forwarding",
            "microsegmentation",
            "domain name resolution",
            "path selection",
            "flow control"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "packet forwarding"
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Consider the IP address configuration shown from PC1. What is a description of the default gateway address?",
        "options": [
            "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the company to the Internet.",
            "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the PC1 LAN to Router1.",
            "It is the IP address of Switch1 that connects PC1 to other devices on the same LAN.",
            "It is the IP address of the ISP network device located in the cloud."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It is the IP address of the Router1 interface that connects the PC1 LAN to Router1."
    },
    {
        "question": "A computer can access devices on the same network but cannot access devices on other networks. What is the probable cause of this problem?",
        "options": [
            "The cable is not connected properly to the NIC.",
            "The computer has an invalid IP address.",
            "The computer has an incorrect subnet mask.",
            "The computer has an invalid default gateway address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The computer has an invalid default gateway address."
    },
    {
        "question": "A router receives an incoming packet and determines that the packet should be forwarded to a remote destination host. What will the router do to forward the packet?",
        "options": [
            "It encapsulates the frame with a source IP address by using the specific IP address of the destination host.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with a destination MAC address by using the specific MAC address of the destination host device.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with the destination IP address by using the specific IP address configured on the interface of the next hop router.",
            "It encapsulates the frame with the destination MAC address by using the MAC address of the interface of the next-hop router."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It encapsulates the frame with the destination MAC address by using the MAC address of the interface of the next-hop router."
    },
    {
        "question": "A router is receiving a stream of incoming packets and does not contain a route to the remote destination network. What configuration can a network administrator issue in order to successfully forward the incoming packets?",
        "options": [
            "Add a default route.",
            "Enable a dynamic routing protocol.",
            "Share the routing table with the hosts on the local network.",
            "Change the IP address of the ingress interface to match the targeted destination network."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Add a default route."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two parts are components of an IPv4 address? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "subnet portion",
            "network portion",
            "logical portion",
            "host portion",
            "physical portion",
            "broadcast portion"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "network portion"
    },
    {
        "question": "When a host sends a packet, how does it determine if the destination of the packet is on the same local network or on a remote network?",
        "options": [
            "It checks to see if the default gateway is configured.",
            "It compares the source and destination MAC addresses.",
            "It queries the DNS server with the destination IP address.",
            "It uses the subnet mask to compare the source and destination IP address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It uses the subnet mask to compare the source and destination IP address."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default subnet mask for an IP address of 198.133.219.4?",
        "options": [
            "255.0.0.0",
            "255.255.0.0",
            "255.255.255.0",
            "255.255.255.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "255.255.255.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three IP addresses are private ? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "10.1.1.1",
            "172.32.5.2",
            "192.167.10.10",
            "172.16.4.4",
            "192.168.5.5",
            "224.6.6.6"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10.1.1.1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of message is sent to a specific group of hosts?",
        "options": [
            "unicast",
            "dynamic",
            "multicast",
            "broadcast"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "multicast"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which IP address is a unicast address if a default subnet mask is used?",
        "options": [
            "201.34.45.0",
            "192.16.43.67",
            "226.34.15.78",
            "195.124.45.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "192.16.43.67"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three types of nodes should be assigned static IP addresses on a network? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "servers",
            "desktop PCs",
            "mobile laptops",
            "printers",
            "gateways",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "servers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is DHCP for IPv4 preferred for use on large networks?",
        "options": [
            "Large networks send more requests for domain to IP address resolution than do smaller networks.",
            "DHCP uses a reliable transport layer protocol.",
            "It prevents sharing of files that are copyrighted.",
            "It is a more efficient way to manage IPv4 addresses than static address assignment is.",
            "Hosts on large networks require more IPv4 addressing configuration settings than do hosts on small networks."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It is a more efficient way to manage IPv4 addresses than static address assignment is."
    },
    {
        "question": "Refer to the exhibit. PC1 is configured to obtain a dynamic IP address from the DHCP server. PC1 has been shut down for two weeks. When PC1 boots and tries to request an available IP address, which destination IP address will PC1 place in the IP header?",
        "options": [
            "192.168.1.1",
            "192.168.1.8",
            "192.168.1.255",
            "255.255.255.255"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "255.255.255.255"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which message does an IPv4 host use to reply when it receives a DHCPOFFER message from a DHCP server?",
        "options": [
            "DHCPACK",
            "DHCPDISCOVER",
            "DHCPOFFER",
            "DHCPREQUEST"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DHCPREQUEST"
    },
    {
        "question": "A host PC is attempting to lease an address through DHCP. What message is sent by the server to let the client know it is able to use the provided IP information?",
        "options": [
            "DHCPDISCOVER",
            "DHCPOFFER",
            "DHCPREQUEST",
            "DHCPACK",
            "DHCPNACK"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DHCPACK"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is a DHCPDISCOVER transmitted on a network to reach a DHCP server?",
        "options": [
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the IP address of the DHCP server as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with a multicast IP address that all DHCP servers listen to as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the broadcast IP address as the destination address.",
            "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the IP address of the default gateway as the destination address."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A DHCPDISCOVER message is sent with the broadcast IP address as the destination address."
    },
    {
        "question": "A DHCP server is used to assign IP addresses dynamically to the hosts on a network. The address pool is configured with 172.30.8.0/24. There are 7 printers on this network that need to use reserved static IP addresses from the pool. How many IP addresses in the pool are left to be assigned to other hosts?",
        "options": [
            "254",
            "247",
            "251",
            "249"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "247"
    },
    {
        "question": "An employee is having connectivity issues. Why might a network technician try to ping the default gateway from the employee laptop?",
        "options": [
            "to verify that an IP address was provided by the DHCP server",
            "to determine if the laptop address is included in the DNS server",
            "to verify that the SVI interface on the switch is configured correctly",
            "to verify connectivity with the device that provides access to remote networks"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to verify connectivity with the device that provides access to remote networks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result if the default gateway address is misconfigured on a PC?",
        "options": [
            "The PC cannot communicate with any devices.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices both in remote networks and in the same network.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices in the same network but not with those in remote networks.",
            "The PC can communicate with devices in remote networks but not with those in the same network."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The PC can communicate with devices in the same network but not with those in remote networks."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement accurately describes dynamic NAT?",
        "options": [
            "It always maps a private IP address to a public IP address.",
            "It provides an automated mapping of inside local to inside global IP addresses.",
            "It provides a mapping of internal host names to IP addresses.",
            "It dynamically provides IP addressing to internal hosts."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It provides an automated mapping of inside local to inside global IP addresses."
    },
    {
        "question": "What purpose does NAT64 serve in IPv6?",
        "options": [
            "It converts IPv6 packets into IPv4 packets.",
            "It translates private IPv6 addresses into public IPv6 addresses.",
            "It enables companies to use IPv6 unique local addresses in the network.",
            "It converts regular IPv6 addresses into 64-bit addresses that can be used on the Internet.",
            "It converts the 48-bit MAC address into a 64-bit host address that can be used for automatic host addressing."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It converts IPv6 packets into IPv4 packets."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of IPv6 address is not routable and used only for communication on a single subnet?",
        "options": [
            "global unicast address",
            "link-local address",
            "loopback address",
            "unique local address",
            "unspecified address"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "link-local address"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bits make up the single IPv6 hextet :10CD:?",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "8",
            "16",
            "32"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the valid most compressed format possible of the IPv6 address 2001:0DB8:0000:AB00:0000:0000:0000:1234?",
        "options": [
            "2001:DB8:0:AB00::1234",
            "2001:DB8:0:AB::1234",
            "2001:DB8::AB00::1234",
            "2001:DB8:0:AB:0:1234"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2001:DB8:0:AB00::1234"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three pieces of information are identified by a URL? (Choose three.)",
        "options": [
            "the MAC address of the web server",
            "the protocol that is being used",
            "the domain name that is being accessed",
            "the IP address of the gateway",
            "the version of the browser",
            "the location of the resource"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the protocol that is being used"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an advantage of UDP over TCP?",
        "options": [
            "UDP communication requires less overhead.",
            "UDP communication is more reliable.",
            "UDP reorders segments that are received out of order.",
            "UDP acknowledges received data."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "UDP communication requires less overhead."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of applications are best suited to use UDP as the transport layer protocol?",
        "options": [
            "applications that require flow control",
            "applications that require data to be reassembled in a specific order",
            "applications that require minimal transmission delay",
            "applications that require stateful sessions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "applications that require minimal transmission delay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What layer of the TCP/IP suite makes sure that all the data packets of a message arrive safely at the destination?",
        "options": [
            "internet",
            "transport",
            "application",
            "network access"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "transport"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does a client computer determine what source port number to assign to a UDP header?",
        "options": [
            "The port number is random within the range of dynamic port numbers.",
            "The port number is based on the application that created the data.",
            "The port number is based on a well-known port number that is open on the destination device.",
            "The port number is based on a well-known port number that is assigned to the application on the sending device."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The port number is random within the range of dynamic port numbers."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a socket?",
        "options": [
            "the combination of the source and destination IP address and source and destination Ethernet address",
            "the combination of a source IP address and port number or a destination IP address and port number",
            "the combination of the source and destination sequence and acknowledgment numbers",
            "the combination of the source and destination sequence numbers and port numbers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the combination of a source IP address and port number or a destination IP address and port number"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using a source port number in a TCP communication?",
        "options": [
            "to notify the remote device that the conversation is over",
            "to assemble the segments that arrived out of order",
            "to keep track of multiple conversations between devices",
            "to inquire for a nonreceived segment"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to keep track of multiple conversations between devices"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two protocols are used in the process of sending and receiving emails? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "HTTP",
            "POP",
            "SSH",
            "SMTP",
            "FTP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "POP"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a function of a DNS server?",
        "options": [
            "It determines the IP address that is associated with a specific host domain name.",
            "It maps IP addresses to physical addresses.",
            "It translates private IP addresses to public IP addresses.",
            "It assigns logical address information to host computers."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "It determines the IP address that is associated with a specific host domain name."
    },
    {
        "question": "Open the PT Activity. Perform the tasks in the activity instructions and then answer the question.",
        "options": [
            "192.168.10.1",
            "192.168.10.100",
            "209.165.201.3",
            "209.165.201.4"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "209.165.201.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Open the PT Activity. Perform the tasks in the activity instructions and then answer the question.",
        "options": [
            "A secure web server is the way to go!",
            "A web server should run secure services!",
            "A web server provides secure communication!",
            "A secure web server is running!"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A secure web server is the way to go!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two applications provide virtual terminal access to remote servers? (Choose two.)",
        "options": [
            "SSH",
            "DNS",
            "DHCP",
            "SMTP",
            "Telnet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "SSH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of server would use IMAP?",
        "options": [
            "DNS",
            "DHCP",
            "email",
            "FTP",
            "Telnet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "email"
    }
]
